SINEM CELENK

MBA Student

HELLO

Enjoys doing market research and finding new market opportunities. Interested in crisis management, data analysis. Has an eye for good design. Stress resilient, good listener and has excellent observation skills. Has broad creative experience with multiple brands such as L'Oréal Paris, Garnier, Kleenex, Huggies, Enterprise.

CONTACT

Phone: +1 604 719 37 01

Mail: celenksinem@gmail.com

Address: 1205 Howe St. Vancouver, BC

Social Media: Linkedin

VOLUNTEERING AFFILIATED ASSOCIATIONS & FOUNDATIONS

- Vancouver General Hospital Information
 Desk Volunteer (VGH) June 2019 to April
 2020
- Vancouver International Jazz Festival
 Environment Team July 2017
- Vancouver Opera Festival Box Office & Information Desk May 2017
- Koruncuk (Turkish Foundation for Children in Need of Protection)
- TOHUM Autism Foundation Turkey

EXPERIENCE

COS Vancouver Part-Time Sales Advisor / Nov 2019 - Current

Delivered an exceptional customer service experience, resolved issues and shared benefits of additional services. Recognized for being positive, intuitive, and client-centric.

Teskilat ICOM Advertising Agency Istanbul

Marketing Specialist / May 2018 - Oct 2018

Managed digital and conventional advertising campaigns for global car rental company. Organized workflow to meet team

campaign and event budgets.

A.N.D.B.R.A.N.D Advertising Agency / Istanbul Marketing Specialist / Nov 2017 - May 2018

Managed advertising campaigns for bank, gas, and technology companies. Organized internal and external meetings, managed budgets.

goals and deadlines. Managed team and client meetings, overall

Essance Istanbul Communication Consultancy

PR Specialist / Feb 2015 - Nov 2016

Developed corporate communications and PR Campaigns for FMCG and local brands. Organized launch parties, conferences and concept events for press and influencers.

EDUCATION

University Canada West / Master of Business Administration (MBA) (2020 – 2022)

Istanbul University / Bachelor Degree of Public Relations and Advertising 3.15/4 (2010 – 2014)

ISS Language and Career College of BC / Professional
Communication and Marketing Diploma Program with CO-OP
(2019 – 2020)

ISS Language and Career College of BC / Business Diploma
Program (May 2017 – July 2017)

EXPERTISE

Marketing
Customer Relationship Management
PR & Advertising
Event, Organization Planning
Administration

Sales
Budget Planning
Social Media
Digital Communication
Crisis Communication

References available upon request.